[{"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上", "下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "toyImg": ["v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg", "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}], [{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input7", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下", "上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-05"}]